<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Risen Technologies</title>
    <link>http://localhost:51646/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Risen Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:51646/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Red Team Operator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/crto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/crto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Holders of the Red Team Operator badge have demonstrated their knowledge of adversary simulation, command &amp;amp; control, engagement planning and time management. They can perform each stage of an attack lifecycle from initial compromise, to full domain takeover, data hunting, and exfiltration; whilst being aware of OPSEC concerns and bypassing defences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/oscp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/oscp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An OSCP has demonstrated the ability to use persistence, creativity, and perceptiveness to identify vulnerabilities and execute organized attacks under tight time constraints. They can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use information gathering techniques to identify and enumerate targets running various operating systems and services&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write scripts and tools to aid in the penetration testing process&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analyze, correct, modify, cross-compile, and port public exploit code&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Conduct remote, local privilege escalation, and client-side attacks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Identify and exploit XSS, SQL injection, and file inclusion vulnerabilities in web applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leverage tunneling techniques to pivot between networks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OSCP holders have also shown they can think outside the box while managing both time and resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/cios/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/cios/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earners of the CompTIA IT Operations Specialist (CIOS) certification have the ability to manage&#xA;the flow of a workplace and optimize day-to-day activities. These IT operations specialists have demonstrated the ability to analyze business operations and identify customer needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/net&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/net&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CompTIA Network+ earners who certified prior to January 1, 2011 have a Network+ considered&#xA;good-for-life (GFL). It does not expire and does not have CE requirements. Earners of the&#xA;CompTIA Network+ certification have the skills needed to troubleshoot, configure, and manage&#xA;enterprise networks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/a&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/about/certifications/a&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CompTIA A+ earners who certified between January 1993 and December 31, 2010, have an A+&#xA;considered good-for-life (GFL). It does not expire and does not have CE requirements. Earners&#xA;of the CompTIA A+ certification have validated skills in hardware repair and configuration, PC&#xA;and peripheral troubleshooting, Windows operating system administration, and user support.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get In Touch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The best ways to reach me are by phone or email.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clubs at River City</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/praise/carc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/praise/carc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am pleased to write this letter of recommendation on behalf of Stephen Redding. I believe he would be a wonderful addition to any business that he is employed at or services. As the main point of contact for Stephen here at the Club, I have had the pleasure of supervising and working with Stephen for over the last couple of years. I have been repeatedly impressed with the depth and thoroughness of Stephen&amp;rsquo;s knowledge and computer skills. He always goes above and beyond to fix whatever issues we may be facing. He always provides a solution to our problems. In addition, he brings a wonderful spirit of cooperation and dedication to his work that makes him an ideal colleague, one who I am sure will contribute positively to your company.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echo Valley Meats</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/praise/echo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/praise/echo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have been working with Stephen Redding for the past few years and have nothing but great things to say about his work, his work ethic and him as a person. Stephen handles our phone systems and just about every computer problem we have at Echo Valley Meats. Stephen is always one phone call away whenever we need him and if he isn’t able to fix our issues remotely he makes sure to stop by our office the same day our service call is placed. He is very skilled and has built multiple programs from scratch for us. We have even had customers in our office while Stephen has been here working who have asked for his contact information because he left such a great impression with them while he was here working on our systems. Stephen shows up for us whenever he is needed and excels at his job. We would recommend him over and over again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enviro-Safe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/praise/envirosafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/praise/envirosafe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Stephen does marvelous IT work. He works quickly and efficiently to solve the myriad of problems thrown at him. We have employed his services for several years, and he keeps improving. Stephen works on small issues like printer connections and works up to the big issues like fixing servers and QuickBooks. It is nice to be able to call and receive a timely response when things are going haywire.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GyrFarm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/praise/gryfarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/praise/gryfarm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have had Stephen working on our equipment for several years now. He came highly recommended by our accountant and we can see why. He is excellent at troubleshooting and doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop until he has success. He has worked on our computers, printers, and closed circuit TV system. He is very knowledgeable, polite, and respectful. We highly recommend him for any of your IT needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koala Center for Sleep &amp; TMJ Disorders</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/praise/koala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/praise/koala/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am pleased to write this letter of recommendation for Stephen Redding. He has provided IT service at our dental practice for many years. Not only does Stephen bring the knowledge necessary to handle all of our IT needs, we appreciate his ability to communicate in a pleasant and professional manner. He is able to explain the problem, provide a solution, and then promptly follows up after the fact letting us know what he encountered and how he corrected the issue. He makes solid recommendations that will help us to avoid such issues in the future. We also appreciate that he is fast at his work. Because he has such vast knowledge, he does not have to work through trial and error to find the solution. He handles it and gets it done correctly the first time. This is not only time-saving and necessary for a busy practice who relies on cloud-based software, but money wise as well. I believe you would be very pleased to have him assist you with all of your IT needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkinnerAg Solutions, Inc</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/praise/skinner-ag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/praise/skinner-ag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As an owner of a small but growing business, we have been faced with an abundance of IT/computer related challenges over the past several years. We have been fortunate to work with Stephen Redding for multiple needs including internet security, software management/assistance, server design and set up, new computer/hardware set up, virus issues and several password recoveries. He is incredibly knowledgeable, very responsive, friendly, and works tirelessly until the problem is resolved. Stephen has been a tremendous asset for our business, and we are certain that he will be of benefit for you as well. We highly recommend him for your IT needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titan Fitness</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51646/praise/titan-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51646/praise/titan-fitness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My experience with Stephen&amp;rsquo;s IT customer service has been a very positive one. He&amp;rsquo;s very honest, knowledgeable and his response time when I have called for help is always fast. He either gets here promptly to fix our IT problem or talks me through a minor issue over the phone. Keeping our budget in mind, he explains options to us when there is something new to install or replace. As a manager of a mid-sized gym where I wear lots of hats, it is very reassuring to me to know that I can rely on Stephen to address our IT issues, keeping us compliant and everything IT related running smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
